

Archana Mulye

Sales And Project Coordinator

Contact

Address

Chembur, India 400071

Phone

7738519510

E-mail

archanamulye613@gmail.co m

Skills

Problem solving strength

Upper intermediate

Network development

Intermediate

Software

MS-Office, Windows and Excel

Upper intermediate

Languages

Marathi

A results driven, self-motivated and resourceful project coordinator with an in depth understanding of all aspects of project coordination and implementation. Experience of supporting the delivery of new and existing products and business enhancements that enable individuals and organizations to improve the quality and productivity. Well presented with excellent communication skills and having a commercial approach to solving problems and developing business. Now looking forward to a making a significant contribution with an ambitious company that offers opportunities for progression.

Work History

2022-11 -Current

Sales and Project Coordinator

Digiconics Enterprise Solutions Pvt Ltd, Navi Mumbai

- Generating leads by doing mass mailing of introduction letter and cold calling.
- Preparing budgetary/tender/short supply offers.
- Follow up with customer for negotiation or any further commercial terms against offer and purchase order.
- Follow up with customer for payment after sharing Proforma Invoice.
- Follow up with vendor for delivery of supply material and inform delivery schedule to customer.
- Preparing technical proposals for OEMs.
- Project coordination and implementation and delivery.
- Coordinate sales team by managing schedules, filing important documents and communicating relevant information.
- Handle the processing of all orders with accuracy and timeliness.
- Inform clients of unforeseen delays or problems.
- Monitor the team's progress, identify shortcomings and propose improvements.
- Helping in achieving sales goals and maintaining positive customer relations.
- handles administrative tasks for the project manager and team members to keep the project running smoothly.

2019-04 -2023-11

Sr. Project Coordinator

Radix Electro systems Pvt Ltd, Navi Mumbai

Advanced

Hindi

Advanced

English

Upper intermediate

- Project Plans: Assist project managers in producing project plans & there after maintaining plans through check point meetings as well, moreover ensuring that the plans are kept up to date.
- Identifying the risks and analyzing opportunities, resolving cross functional issues at project level & communicating with the managers & team as well.
- Participating in reviews meetings & providing updates on daily basis. Assist with determination of projects requirement and procurement management.
- Managing project deliverable in line with the project plan which is given to the management.
- Inter-department coordination to ensure smooth functioning of project deliveries. Effectively & accurately communicate relevant information about the project to the team.
- Assisting & supporting the project manager on daily basis.
- Acting as a link between automation dept & assign tasks to internal teams, further assist with schedule management.
- Involved in coordinating project from the beginning till the end.
- Monitor project progress and handle any issues that arise.
- Create and maintain comprehensive project documentation, plans and reports.
- Provide directions & support to the Team in absence of project manager.
- Use tools (ERP & Zoho) to monitor working hours, plans and expenditures, break projects into doable actions and additionally set time frames.
- Actively look for opportunities to improve current progress.
- Coordination for service related matters with vendors & Radix internal automation team, simultaneously with Radix service team for service estimation which needs to be provided to the client.
- Also, participating in Automation Store Stock Audit, by giving accountability of last month projects which was not able to be delivered on time.

2014-03 -2019-03

Project Coordinator

Radix Electro systems Pvt Ltd, Navi Mumbai

- Assisting & supporting the project manager on daily basis.
- Acting as a link between automation dept & assign tasks to internal teams.
- Involved in coordinating project from the beginning till the end.
- Monitor project progress and handle any issues that arise.
- Provide directions & support to the Team in absence of project manager.
- Used tools ERP.
- Coordination for service related matters with vendors & Radix internal automation team, simultaneously with Radix service team for service estimation which needs to be provided to the client.
- Also, participating in Automation Store Stock Audit, by giving accountability of last month projects which was not able to be delivered on time.

2013-05 -2014-03

Project Executive

GOMA Engineering Pvt. Ltd, Thane

- Taking quotation from different vendors for the project execution & making comparisons.
- Arrange techno-commercial meeting with vendors & giving orders.
- Negotiation with vendors & after coordination with marketing dept about selling price, then generate purchase order along with proper technical specification.
- Arrange vendor payment & follow up for material readiness.
- Arrange the transporter to dispatch the materials from vendor to project site or Head Office.
- Making coordination with the inter department about project execution & dispatch.
- Maintain necessary documentation & cross check.
- Helping to marketing department to take quotations from vendors to fill up the tenders before due date.

2012-02 -2013-05

Import-Export Sales Executive-Instrumentation Dept

PCI Analytics PVT. LTD, Bhandup

- Making of Quotations accordingly as preorders.
- Generate enquiries as per requirement of foreign customer.
- Provide technical support to clients.
- Payment Processing of both Import & Export.
- Providing them the same high level of customer service and technical expertise that this organization is known for.
- Making of monthly reports that we can use in future also.
- Purchase Order Processing for Instruments and Equipments.
- Preparation of Export Documentation.
- Import materials from foreign countries.
- Finding dealers/ distributors/ suppliers from foreign countries for the related product.
- Making Good Relations with foreign customers.
- Preparation for Exhibition.
- Arranging meetings at both internal and external locations with Clients.
- Understanding of complex technical products.
- Preparation of monthly reports.
- Arranging meetings with Clients.
- Maintain the documents of daily, weekly, fortnightly and monthly of instrumental equipment's.

Education

2006-04 -	BE: Instrumentation
2010-06	Konkan Gyan Peeth College of Engineering - Karjat
2004-06 -	HSC: Science
2006-02	Birla College - Kalyan
2003-06 -	SSC: All Subjects
2004-03	Nutan Dnyan Madir - Kalyan

Certifications

2023-04 Power BI

Interpersonal Skills:

- Self motivated with a flexible attitude and always able to adapt quickly to the change.
- Leading, engaging and building confidence in project staff.
- Having exceptional interpersonal, communication and motivational skills. .
- Willing to learn new things.

Personal Information

Nationality: Indian

Date of Birth: 06th June 1989

Marital Status: Married

Overall Experience: 10 years

Hobbies: Cooking, Trekking, Dancing